<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Operating System on Changelog Wiki</title>
    <link>/tags/operating-system/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Operating System on Changelog Wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>MIT Licensed</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/tags/operating-system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Switch v4.0.0 Update</title>
      <link>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-10-18-v4.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-10-18-v4.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Added the following system functionality:
 Capture video on select games  To capture video, hold down the Capture Button during gameplay Up to a maximum of the previous 30 seconds will be saved in the Album. You can trim the beginning and end of each clip, and post to Facebook and Twitter. As of October 18, 2017, this feature is compatible with The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild, Mario Kart 8 Deluxe, ARMS, and Splatoon 2   Select from 12 new Super Mario Odyssey and The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild icons for your user  To edit your user icon, head to your My Page on the top-left of the Home Menu and select Profile   Transfer user and save data to another system  To transfer, head to System Settings, Users, then Transfer Your User and Save Data   Pre-purchase option on Nintendo eShop  A pre-purchase option will be available for certain games.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Switch v3.0.2 Update</title>
      <link>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-09-05-v3.0.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-09-05-v3.0.2/</guid>
      <description>Nintendo Switch Online  Added online play in Argentina, Brazil, Chile, Colombia, and Peru. This is currently available for free until the paid online service launches in 2018.   General system stability improvements to enhance the user&amp;rsquo;s experience  Source: https://en-americas-support.nintendo.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/43314</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Switch v3.0.2 Update</title>
      <link>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-07-31-v3.0.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-07-31-v3.0.1/</guid>
      <description>General system stability improvements to enhance the user&amp;rsquo;s experience, including:
 Addressed an issue in which the remaining battery charge can&amp;rsquo;t be displayed accurately  If the system&amp;rsquo;s battery power display suddenly increases or decreases, it will gradually improve by following these steps from our troubleshooting guide.    Source: https://en-americas-support.nintendo.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/43314</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Switch v3.0.0 Update</title>
      <link>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-06-19-v3.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-06-19-v3.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Added the following system functionality
 Register a channel to receive News for specific games  To register, head to News, then Find Channels   Add friends from your Nintendo 3DS and Wii U Friend Lists  To add friends, head to your My Page on the top-left of the Home Menu and select Friend Suggestions   Receive notifications when your Friends go online  To turn this ON/OFF, head to System Settings, Notifications, then Friend Notifications   Find paired controllers within communication range by activating the vibration feature  To search, head to Controllers, then Find Controllers   Change the user icon order on the Home Menu  To change order, head to System Settings, Users, then Change Order   Select from 6 new Splatoon 2 characters for user icon  To edit your user icon, head to your My Page on the top-left of the Home Menu and select Profile   Change the system volume from the Quick Settings  To access Quick Settings, hold down the HOME Button   The maximum volume when using headphones or speakers connected to the audio jack has been raised and can be lowered if desired.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Switch v2.3.0 Update</title>
      <link>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-05-17-v2.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-05-17-v2.3.0/</guid>
      <description>General system stability improvements to enhance the user&amp;rsquo;s experience  Source: https://en-americas-support.nintendo.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/43314</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Switch v2.2.0 Update</title>
      <link>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-04-17-v2.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-04-17-v2.2.0/</guid>
      <description>General system stability improvements to enhance the user&amp;rsquo;s experience  Source: https://en-americas-support.nintendo.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/43314</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Switch v2.1.0 Update</title>
      <link>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-03-27-v2.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-03-27-v2.1.0/</guid>
      <description>General system stability improvements to enhance the user&amp;rsquo;s experience  Source: https://en-americas-support.nintendo.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/43314</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nintendo Switch v2.0.0 Update</title>
      <link>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-03-03-v2.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/nintendo-switch/nintendo-switch/2017-03-03-v2.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Nintendo Account required. Some features may not be available in all countries/regions.
 Playing online  Online multiplayer available for free until the paid online service launches in 2018. Not available in all countries.   Adding friends  Friends can be added from My Page, head to the HOME Menu and select your icon on the upper left.   Sharing Album screenshots to Facebook and Twitter Browsing and purchasing content on Nintendo eShop Receiving News relating to games, Nintendo eShop discounts, and promotions Earning My Nintendo points for game card (retail version)  Added the following system functionality:</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
